{
"question": "青",
"answer": "あお"
},
{
"question": "靴下",
"answer": "くつした"
},
{
"question": "封筒",
"answer": "ふうとう"
},
{
"question": "辺",
"answer": "へん"
},
{
"question": "黄色",
"answer": "きいろ"
},
{
"question": "映画館",
"answer": "えいがかん"
},
{
"question": "箸",
"answer": "はし"
},
{
"question": "食堂",
"answer": "しょくどう"
},
{
"question": "牛肉",
"answer": "ぎゅうにく"
},
{
"question": "交差点",
"answer": "こうさてん"
},
{
"question": "漢字",
"answer": "かんじ"
},
{
"question": "茶わん",
"answer": "ちゃわん"
},
{
"question": "曇り",
"answer": "くもり"
},
{
"question": "背広",
"answer": "せびろ"
},
{
"question": "灰皿",
"answer": "はいざら"
},
{
"question": "万年筆",
"answer": "まんねんひつ"
},
{
"question": "大使館",
"answer": "たいしかん"
},
{
"question": "交番",
"answer": "こうばん"
},
{
"question": "豚肉",
"answer": "ぶたにく"
},
{
"question": "飲む",
"answer": "のむ"
},
